<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LAB_WEEK_04</string>
    <string name="app_title">Coffee App</string>

    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation Header</string>

    <string name="menu_coffee">Coffee List</string>
    <string name="menu_favorites">Favorite Coffee</string>

    <string name="affogato_title">AFFOGATO</string>
    <string name="affogato_desc">Espresso poured on a vanilla ice cream. Served in a cappuccino cup.</string>

    <string name="americano_title">AMERICANO</string>
    <string name="americano_desc">Espresso with added hot water (100-150 ml). Often served in a cappuccino cup. (The espresso is added into the hot water rather than all the water being flowed through the coffee that would lead to over extraction)</string>

    <string name="latte_title">LATTE</string>
    <string name="latte_desc">A tall, mild milk coffee (about 150-300 ml). An espresso drink with steamed milk and only a little milk foam poured over it. Serve in a latte glass or a coffee cup. Flavoured syrup can be added.</string>

    <string name="cappuccino_title">CAPPUCCINO</string>
    <string name="cappuccino_desc">A popular coffee drink with equal parts espresso, steamed milk, and milk foam. Usually served in a cappuccino cup.</string>

    <string name="mocha_title">MOCHA</string>
    <string name="mocha_desc">Espresso mixed with hot chocolate, topped with steamed milk and whipped cream. Served in a tall glass or a coffee cup.</string>

    <string name="macchiato_title">MACCHIATO</string>
    <string name="macchiato_desc">Espresso stained with a dash of steamed milk or foam. Usually served in an espresso cup.</string>

    <string name="espresso_title">ESPRESSO</string>
    <string name="espresso_desc">A strong, concentrated coffee brewed by forcing hot water through finely-ground coffee beans. Served in a small espresso cup.</string>

    <string name="flat_white_title">FLAT WHITE</string>
    <string name="flat_white_desc">An espresso-based drink with steamed milk but little to no foam, creating a smoother texture. Served in a small cup.</string>

    <string name="cold_brew_title">COLD BREW</string>
    <string name="cold_brew_desc">Coffee brewed with cold water over a long period (usually 12-24 hours). Served cold, often with ice and milk.</string>

    <string name="ristretto_title">RISTRETTO</string>
    <string name="ristretto_desc">A shorter and more concentrated version of espresso, made with less water, resulting in a more intense flavor. Served in an espresso cup.</string>

    <string name="coffee_list">Coffee List</string>
    <string name="coffee_favorites">My Favorite Coffee</string>
    <string name="cafe_list">Cafe List</string>

    <string name="bottom_menu_coffee">Coffee</string>
    <string name="bottom_menu_cafe">Cafe</string>

    <string name="starbucks_title">STARBUCKS</string>
    <string name="starbucks_desc">Starbucks Corporation is an American multinational chain of coffeehouses and roastery reserves headquartered in Seattle, Washington. It is the world\'s largest coffeehouse chain.</string>
    <string name="janjijiwa_title">JANJI JIWA</string>
    <string name="janjijiwa_desc">It is undeniable that Janji Jiwa outlets have spread to various corners. Janji Jiwa is a local coffee brand that is popular among students, students, workers and even families. Carrying the jargon "coffee from the heart", Janji Jiwa is committed to serving coffee with a classic taste for coffee lovers.</string>
    <string name="kopikenangan_title">KOPI KENANGAN</string>
    <string name="kopikenangan_desc">At Kopi Kenangan, their dream is to serve high quality coffee, made with the freshest local ingredients to customers across Indonesia – and the rest of the world</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
